Inventory of the Class Reunion Books Collection, 1856 - [ongoing]
Class Reunion Books Collection, 1856 - [ongoing]
Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)
1000-156
4
8
Wesleyan University began holding reunions for its alumni in the late 1860s. Prior to that, alumni stayed in touch with one another through correspondence. The University began compiling news and events related to its graduates beginning in the 1850s, and these collections of updates were frequently gathered into volumes distributed to class members.
The Class Reunion Books typically contain letters or information from alumni with news of their families, careers, and other updates. They also contain reminiscences of Wesleyan. Later books frequently include photographs.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisitions Information
Transferred from University Relations on periodic basis.
Historical Note
Wesleyan University began holding reunions for its alumni in the late 1860s. Prior to that, alumni stayed in touch with one another through correspondence. The University began compiling news and events related to its graduates beginning in the 1850s, and these collections of updates were frequently gathered into volumes distributed to class members.
Collection Overview
The Class Reunion Books typically contain letters or information from alumni with news of their families, careers, and other updates. They also contain reminiscences of Wesleyan. Later books frequently include photographs.
Collection Arrangement
Materials are arranged chronologically by year of graduation.
Online Catalog Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Alumni and alumnae.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--History.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Students.; Class reunions --United States.; Photographs.
Related Material
More biographical information about alumni can be found in Wesleyan University's Alumni Records or Alumni Directories, published approximately once every ten years since the 1880s.
The Vertical Files Collection in Wesleyan's Special Collections & Archives also contains biographical information about alumni.
Detailed Description of the Collection
  - Class of 1856
    - Chronicles for the Year 1856-1857 (Box 1)
    - Chronicles for the Year 1858-1859 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1858
    - 21 Years, 1879 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1860
    - Annual Records, 1861-1862 (Box 1)
    - Annual Records, 1864 (Box 1)
    - Annual Records, 1865 (Box 1)
    - Annual Records, 1867 (Box 1)
    - Reunion and Records, 40th Reunion, 1900 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1863
    - Annual Records, date unknown (Box 1)
    - Annual Records, 1870 (Box 1)
    - 40th Reunion, 1903 (Box 1)
    - 50th Reunion, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1865
    - 1900 (Box 1)
    - Class History, 40th Reunion, 1905 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1870
    - Records, date unknown (Box 1)
  - Class of 1887
    - Five Years, 1892 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1889
    - Thanksgiving Broadcast, 1945 (Box 2)
    - Broadcast, 1946 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1892
    - The First 50 Years, 1942 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1893
    - 29th Anniversary, 1922 (Box 2)
    - 35th Anniversary, 1928 (Box 2)
    - 40th Anniversary, 1933 (Box 2)
    - 50th Anniversary Memorial Service, 1943 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1896
    - Records, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1903
    - 25th Reunion, 1928 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1907
    - Haddam Again, 10th Reunion, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1912
    - Class Day, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1914
    - 10th Reunion Memorial Report, 1924 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1914
    - 25th Reunion, 1939 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1920
    - Minutes (Sophomore Year), 1917-1918 (Box 3)
    - Milepost 50, 1970 (Box 3)
    - 50th Reunion Class List, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1924
    - 55 Year History, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1928
    - 50th Reunion, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1929
    - 50th Reunion, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1930
    - Fifty Year History, 1980 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1932
    - 50th Reunion, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1933
    - 50th Reunion, 1983 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1934
    - 55th Reunion List of Living Members, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1935
    - 45th Reunion, 1980 (Box 3)
    - 50th Reunion, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1936
    - 50th Reunion, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1937
    - 50th Reunion, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1938
    - 40th Reunion, 1978 (Box 4)
    - 50th Reunion, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1939
    - 50th Reunion, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1940
    - 50th Reunion, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1941
    - 50th Reunion, 1991 (Box 4)
    - 65th Reunion, 2006 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1942
    - 50th Reunion, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1943
    - 50th Reunion, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1944
    - 50th Reunion, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1945
    - News Book, 55th Reunion, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1946
    - 50th Reunion, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1947
    - 50th Reunion, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1948
    - 50th Reunion, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1949
    - 30 Year History, 1979 (Box 5)
    - 50th Reunion, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1950
    - 50th Reunion, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1951
    - 50th Reunion, 2001 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1952
    - 45th Reunion, 1997 (Box 5)
    - 50th Reunion, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1953
    - 50th Reunion, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1954
    - 50th Reunion, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1955
    - 50th Reunion, 2005 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1956
    - 10th Annual Report, 1966 (Box 6)
    - 50th Reunion, 2006 (Box 6)
  - Class of 1957
    - 20th Reunion, 1977 (Box 6)
    - 40th Reunion, 1997 (Box 6)
    - 50th Reunion, 2007 (Box 6)
  - Class of 1960
    - 20th Reunion, 1980 (Box 6)
  - Class of 1961
    - 50th Reunion, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Class of 1962
    - 25th Reunion, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Class of 1963
    - 15 Year History, 1978 (Box 6)
    - 25th Reunion, 1988 (Box 6)
    - 35th Reunion, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Class of 1964
    - 25th Reunion, 1989 (Box 6)
    - 35th Reunion, 1999 (Box 6)
  - Class of 1965
    - 35th Reunion, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1966
    - 10th Reunion Yearbook, 1976 (Box 7)
    - 30th Reunion Yearbook, 1996 (Box 7)
    - 35th Reunion Yearbook, 2001 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1968
    - 25th Reunion Class Directory, 1993 (Box 7)
    - 30th Reunion Class Directory, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1969
    - 10 Year History, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1970
    - 10 Year History, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1972
    - 25th Reunion, 1997 (Box 7)
    - 30th Reunion, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1973
    - 25th Reunion, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1974
    - 5 Year History, 1979 (Box 7)
    - 25th Reunion, 1999 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1975
    - 5 Year History, 1980 (Box 7)
    - 25th Reunion, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1976
    - 20th Reunion, 1996 (Box 8)
    - 25th Reunion, 2001 (Box 8)
  - Class of 1977
    - 25th Reunion, 2002 (Box 8)
  - Class of 1978
    - 25th Reunion, 2003 (Box 8)
  - Class of 1979
    - 25th Reunion, 2004 (Box 8)
  - Class of 1980
    - 25th Reunion, 2005 (Box 8)
  - Class of 1981
    - 25th Reunion, 2006 (Box 8)
  - Class of 1982
    - 25th Reunion, 2007 (Box 8)
  - Class of 1986
    - 10th Reunion, 1996 (Box 8)